A Guide to the R. Bruce Merrifield papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA415
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Manuscripts and Publications, 5
  - The Automatic Synthesis of Proteins (Box 292, Folder 1836)
  - Barany, George (Box 292, Folder 1837-1839)
  - Barany, PNAS (Box 293, Folder 1840)
  - Barany, PNAS (Box 293, Folder 1840A)
  - Barany, George, and R. Bruce Merrifield, "Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis", 1979 (Box 293, Folder 1841)
  - Beckman "Fractions" Article (Box 293, Folder 1842)
  - Before Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis (Box 293, Folder 1843)
  - "Beitrge zur Synthese und Analyse von Peptiden an Vernetzten Polymeren Trgern" by Birr, 1976 (Box 293, Folder 1844)
  - Binder, C. Unson (Box 294, Folder 1845)
  - "Biophysical Chemistry," Special Issue in Honour of John T. Edsall, 2003 (Box 294, Folder 1846)
  - "Biopolymers: Remembering Bruce Merrifield", 2006-2008 (Box 294, Folder 1847-1850, Box 295, Folder 1851-1857, Box 296, Folder 1858-1862, Box 297, Folder 1863-1867, Box 298, Folder 1868-1871, Box 299, Folder 1872-1875, Box 300, Folder 1876-1878, Box 301, Folder 1879)
  - "The Biosynthesis of Thyroxine" by Yip, 1962 (Box 301, Folder 1880)
  - Blackburn (Box 301, Folder 1881)
  - Blackburn (Box 301, Folder 1881A)
  - Bo (Box 301, Folder 1882)
  - Boffa, Carpaneto, and Allfrey, PNAS (Box 301, Folder 1883)
  - Boffa et al., PNAS (Box 301, Folder 1884)
  - Boffa et al., PNAS (Box 301, Folder 1884A)
  - Bradykinin Reprints (Box 301, Folder 1885)
  - Bradykininylbradykinin (Box 302, Folder 1886)
  - Burley, X-Ray (Box 302, Folder 1887)
  - C&E News Articles (Box 302, Folder 1888)
  - C Gen, 1971 (Box 302, Folder 1889)
  - CA-Me Hybrids, Old Copies, Wade (Box 302, Folder 1890)
  - "The Calcium Binding Protein of the Chick Chorioallantoic Membrane" by Tuan (Box 302, Folder 1891)
  - Cecille's Glucagon-NMR Project (Box 302, Folder 1892)
  - Cecropin ("Synthesis of the Antibacterial Peptide Cecropin A (1-33)") (Box 303, Folder 1983)
  - Cecropin (partial), 1984 (Box 303, Folder 1894)
  - Cecropin A (1-33) Artwork (Box 303, Folder 1895)
  - "The Chemical Structure and Biological Activities of Concanavalin A"by Wang, 1973 (Box 303, Folder 1896)
  - "The Chemical Synthesis of Model Catalysts Related to Enzymes" by Hershey, 1963 (Box 303, Folder 1897)
  - "The Chemical Synthesis of Peptides: A Select Bibliography", 2000 (Box 303, Folder 1898)
  - Chemistry Notes, Papers, for the Proteomic and Innate Ab Problems (Box 303, Folder 1899)
  - Chillemi Manuscript (Box 303, Folder 1900)
  - "Chlorotrimethylsilane-Phenol for Selective Deprotection of the N-tert- Butyloxycarbonyl Group in Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Kaiser et al., Draft (Box 303, Folder 1901)
  - Christensen (Box 303, Folder 1902)
  - "Chromatography, A Century of Discovery, 1900-2000," edited by Gehrke, Wixom, and Bayer (Box 304, Folder 1903)
  - Cited AB Reprints (Box 304, Folder 1904)
  - "Citryl Phosphate and the Mechanism of the Citrate Cleavage Reaction" by Walsh, 1969 (Box 304, Folder 1905)
  - Commitments, 1984 June (Box 304, Folder 1906)
  - Comp Graphics (Box 304, Folder 1907)
  - "Comparative Biochemistry of Drug-Binding Proteins in the Calmodulin/S100 Family" by Marshak, 1983 (Box 305, Folder 1908)
  - "Competitive Inhibition of a Strepogenin-Active Peptide by Related Peptides" by Merrifield (Box 305, Folder 1909)
  - "The Concept and Early Development of Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Merrifield (Box 305, Folder 1910)
  - The Concept and Early Development of Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis Master File, Copy of Corrected Page Proofs, 1993 (Box 305, Folder 1911)
  - "Conformational Studies of the Peptide Antibiotic Polymyxin B by Nuclear Magnetic Resonance" by Bockman, 1971 (Box 305, Folder 1912)
  - "Convergent Synthesis of Dolastatin 15 by Solid Phase Coupling of N-methylamino Acid" by Akaji et al. (Box 306, Folder 1913)
  - COOH-Terminal Peptides (Box 306, Folder 1914)
  - Copy 2, Illustrations (Box 306, Folder 1915)
  - Copy 3, Illustrations (Box 306, Folder 1916)
  - "Couplage Covalent Reversible de la Daunorubicine et de la Primaquine a des Proteines: Application a une Chimiotherapie plus Selective du Cancer et de la Malaria" by Masquelier, 1981 (Box 306, Folder 1917)
  - Cowburn and Muir (Box 306, Folder 1918)
  - Cowburn and Muir (Box 306, Folder 1918A)
  - Cruciani, PNAS (Box 306, Folder 1919)
  - Cruciani, PNAS (Box 306, Folder 1919A)
  - Cypress, Unson, Sakmar, 1999 (Box 307, Folder 1920)
    - Disk, 2016:FA415:008 (Box 307, Folder 1920)
  - Defoort, PNAS (Box 307, Folder 1921)
  - Defoort, PNAS (Box 307, Folder 1921A)
  - De Novo (Box 307, Folder 1922)
  - "Detection of a Peptide Epitope of the MUC2 Tandem Repeat with a Mouse Monoclonal Antibody" by Gambus et al. (Box 307, Folder 1923)
  - "Detection of a Peptide Epitope of the MUC2 Tandem Repeat with a Mouse Monoclonal Antibody" by Gambus et al. (Box 307, Folder 1924)
  - "The Determination of a Proline in Protein Hydrolysates with Lactobacillus Brevis" by Dunn, McClure, and Merrifield, 1948 (Box 307, Folder 1925)
  - "Developing Models and Methods to Study DNA-Protein Noncovalent Binding Interactions" by Walters (Box 307, Folder 1926)
  - "Dielectric Properties of Proteins" by Kirschner, 1967 (Box 307, Folder 1927)
  - Don't Use - Beckman Symposium, 1985 (Box 307, Folder 1928)
  - Draft for Kinetics, 1985 February 20 (Box 307, Folder 1929)
  - Drafts of Papers II and III (Box 307, Folder 1930)
  - Durrah, Tracy L., Protocols for Assays (Box 308, Folder 1930)
  - Early Drafts (Box 308, Folder 1932)
  - Engelhard (Box 308, Folder 1933)
  - Engelhard (Box 308, Folder 1933A)
  - Epand, PNAS (Box 308, Folder 1934)
  - Epand, PNAS (Box 308, Folder 1934A)
  - Erickson, Bruce W. (Box 308, Folder 1935-1936, Box 309, Folder 1937)
  - Erickson Reprints (Box 309, Folder 1938)
  - "Experiments on the Synthesis and Spectral Characterization of Cytochrome-Related Molecules" by Robinson, 1967 (Box 309, Folder 1939)
  - Extra Figures and Tables (Box 309, Folder 1940)
  - Extra Xeroxes of Photos and Figures (Box 309, Folder 1941)
  - Fahmy et al., PNAS (Box 310, Folder 1942)
  - Fahmy et al., PNAS (Box 310, Folder 1942A)
  - Fehlbaum (Box 310, Folder 1943)
  - Felix Manuscript, Azides (Box 310, Folder 1944)
  - Figures (Box 310, Folder 1945)
  - Figures and Tables and Slides (Box 310, Folder 1946)
  - Fox, "Immunoadsorbent Columns: Preparation and Use" (Box 310, Folder 1947)
  - Furlong (Box 310, Folder 1948)
  - Galley Proofs (Box 310, Folder 1949)
  - Gastrinl, Tam (Box 311, Folder 1950)
  - Glass, PNAS (Box 311, Folder 1951)
  - Glass, PNAS (Box 311, Folder 1951A)
  - GB-RBM (George Barany and R. Bruce Merrifield, "Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis"), 1979 (Box 311, Folder 1952)
  - Glass Thesis (Box 311, Folder 1953)
  - Glucagon (Box 311, Folder 1954)
  - Glucagon Antagonists, China (Box 312, Folder 1955)
  - Glucagon Citations, SciFinder Scholar (Box 312, Folder 1956)
  - Glucagon Conformation (Box 312, Folder 1957)
  - Glucagon Paper, Unson and Mojsov (Box 312, Folder 1958)
  - Glucagon Photographs (Box 312, Folder 1959)
  - Glucagon Project (Box 312, Folder 1960)
  - Glucagon Receptor Activates Extracellular (Box 312, Folder 1961)
  - Glucagon References (Box 313, Folder 1962)
  - Glucagon References Conformation II (Box 313, Folder 1963)
  - Glucagon References NMR II (Box 313, Folder 1964)
  - Glucagon Reprints (Box 313, Folder 1965-1966)
  - Glucagon Reprints, 1981-1983 (Box 313, Folder 1967)
  - Glucagon Report, Murphy (Box 313, Folder 1968)
  - Glucagon Review (Box 314, Folder 1969)
  - Glycolaldehyde for PNAS, Acharya and Manning (Box 314, Folder 1970)
  - Glycolaldehyde for PNAS, Acharya and Manning (Box 314, Folder 1970A)
  - Glycyl-L-aspartyl-L-seryl-glycine (Box 314, Folder 1971)
  - Gund, Semisynthesis, PNAS (Box 314, Folder 1972)
  - Gund, Semisynthesis, PNAS (Box 314, Folder 1972A)
  - Gutte and Merrifield, Ribonuclease A (Box 314, Folder 1973)
  - Gutte Reviews (Box 314, Folder 1974)
  - Harvey Lecture (Box 314, Folder 1975)
  - Heath, William F., Jr., Thesis, "A Synthetic Approach to the Structure-Function Relationships in the Murine Epidermal Growth Factor Molecule", 1986 (Box 315, Folder 1976)
  - "High Strepogenin Potency of Synthetic Oxytocin and of Purified Vasopressin" by Woolley and Merrifield (Box 315, Folder 1977)
  - Histone Drafts (Box 315, Folder 1978)
  - "The History of Peptide Chemistry" (Box 315, Folder 1979)
  - "The History of Protein Synthesis" (Box 315, Folder 1980, Box 316, Folder 1981-1984, Box 317, Folder 1985)
  - "The History of Protein Synthesis," Drafts (Box 317, Folder 1986-1987)
  - Hoffman, PNAS (Box 317, Folder 1988)
  - Hoffman, PNAS (Box 317, Folder 1988A)
  - Hopp Manuscript, PNAS (Box 317, Folder 1989)
  - Hopp Manuscript, PNAS (Box 317, Folder 1989A)
  - Houghten (Box 317, Folder 1990)
  - Houghten, PNAS (Box 318, Folder 1991)
  - Houghten, PNAS (Box 318, Folder 1991A)
  - Hruby, PNAS (Box 318, Folder 1992)
  - Hruby, PNAS (Box 318, Folder 1992A)
  - I (Box 318, Folder 1993)
  - IF Reviews (Box 318, Folder 1994)
  - Immunology - Old Version ("Specificity of Antibodies Elicited by a Synthetic Peptide having a Sequence in Common with a Fragment of a Virus Protein - the Hepatitis B Surface Antigen" by Neurath, Kent, and Strick (Box 318, Folder 1995)
  - "Immunoprecipitation of Some Forms of Simian Virus 40 Large-T Antigen by Antibodies to Synthetic Peptides" by Paucha, Harvey, and Smith (Box 318, Folder 1996)
  - "Improvements and Extensions of the Solid Phase Peptide Method" by A.R. Mitchell, 1973 (Box 318, Folder 1997)
  - "Inhibition of the Classical Complement Pathway by Synthetic Peptides from the C2 Domain of Immunoglobulin G" by Prystowsky, 1978 (Box 318, Folder 1998-1999)
  - "Innate Antibody Project" (Box 318, Folder 2000)
  - Insulin (Box 319, Folder 2001)
  - Insulin, Katsoyannis (Box 319, Folder 2002)
  - Insulin, Zahn (Box 319, Folder 2003)
  - "Investigations of Amino Acids, Peptides, and Proteins" (XIX-XXVIII) (Box 319, Folder 2004)
  - Interferon Abstract, Heidelberg (Box 319, Folder 2005)
  - Intra-Science (Box 319, Folder 2006)
  - "Isolation and Determination of Structure of a Peptide with Strepogenin Activity" (Box 319, Folder 2007)
  - "The Isolation and Determination of Structure of Peptides with Strepogenin Activity I. Serylhistidylleucylvalylglutamic Acid and Serylhistidylleucylvalylglutamylalanylleucine from Insulin" by Merrifield and Woolley (Box 319, Folder 2008)
  - The Isolation of A and B Chain Sulfonates of Insulin by Countercurrent Distribution (Box 319, Folder 2009)
  - J (Box 319, Folder 2010)
  - Jennings and Kemp, PNAS (Box 319, Folder 2011)
  - Jennings and Kemp, PNAS (Box 319, Folder 2011A)
  - Jimmy's Corrections on Emil's Paper (and Francis) (Box 320, Folder 2012)
  - Journal of the American Medical Association, Lasker (Box 320, Folder 2013)
  - Journal of Peptide Research (Box 320, Folder 2014)
  - Journals (Box 320, Folder 2015)
  - Jung, Gnther (Box 320, Folder 2016)
  - K (Box 320, Folder 2017)
  - Kaiser (Box 320, Folder 2018, Box 321, Folder 2019-2020)
  - Kaiser (Box 321, Folder 2020A)
  - Kaiser, Emil (Box 321, Folder 2021-2022)
  - Kaiser, Emil, 1984 October 2 (Box 321, Folder 2023)
  - Kaiser, Emil, CTMS (Chlorotrimethylsilane) New Data, 1987 November 9 (Box 322, Folder 2024)
  - Kaiser Manuscript ("Chlorotrimethylsilane-Phenol as a Selective Deprotection Reagent for the N-Butyloxycarbonyl Group in Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis") (Box 322, Folder 2025)
  - Kaiser Reprints (Box 322, Folder 2026)
  - Kaiser Silanolate (Box 322, Folder 2027)
  - Katsoyannis, PNAS (Box 322, Folder 2028)
  - Katsoyannis, PNAS (Box 322, Folder 2028A)
  - Kemp, PNAS (Box 322, Folder 2029-2030)
  - Kemp, PNAS (Box 322, Folder 2030A)
  - Kent, RNase (Box 322, Folder 2031)
  - Khan, Shabbir, PNAS (Box 323, Folder 3032)
  - Khan, Shabbir, PNAS (Box 323, Folder 2032A)
  - King, T.P., Melittin (Box 323, Folder 2033)
  - Krstenansky, PNAS (Box 323, Folder 2034)
  - Kubiak (Box 323, Folder 2035)
  - L (Box 323, Folder 2036)
  - Lab Reprints (Box 323, Folder 2037-2038)
  - Lerner (Box 323, Folder 2039)
  - Library (of) Medicine Prints (Box 324, Folder 2040)
  - Ligation and Fragment Synthesis, VI A1D.5 (Box 324, Folder 2041)
  - "Lithium-Salt Effects in Peptide Synthesis, Park II" by Thaler, Seebach, and Cardinaux (Box 324, Folder 2042)
  - Live, David - NMR - Resin Proposal (Box 324, Folder 2043)
  - "Local Sequence and Folding: The -Turn as a Role Model" by Rotondi, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 2044)
  - M (Box 325, Folder 2045-2046)
  - Magazine Articles: Meetings, etc. (Box 325, Folder 2047)
  - Manning, PNAS (Box 325, Folder 2048)
  - Manning, PNAS (Box 325, Folder 2048A)
  - Meek, James L. (Box 325, Folder 2049)
  - Meek, James L. (Box 325, Folder 2049A)
  - Meinhofer Old Version, 1994 (Box 325, Folder 2050)
  - Merrifield, R.B., "History of Protein Synthesis" (Box 326, Folder 2051)
  - Merrifield, R.B., "History of Protein Synthesis," Thieme Materials (Box 326, Folder 2052)
  - Microbiological Publications of M.S. Dunn (Box 326, Folder 2053)
  - Mitsuya and Tager, PNAS (Box 326, Folder 2054)
  - Mitsuya and Tager, PNAS (Box 326, Folder 2054A)
  - "Modeling the Ion Channel Structure of Cecropin" by Durrell, Raghunathan, and Guy (Box 326, Folder 2055)
  - Mojsov, PNAS (Box 326, Folder 2056)
  - Mojsov, PNAS (Box 326, Folder 2056A)
  - "Molecular Determinants of Glucagon Receptor Signaling" by Cecilia G. Unson (Box 326, Folder 2057)
  - My Reviews (Box 326, Folder 2058)
  - N (Box 326, Folder 2059)
  - National Institute of General Medical Sciences, 1969 (Box 327, Folder 2060)
  - NGF (Nerve Growth Factor) Paper (Box 327, Folder 2061)
  - Neurath and Kent, PNAS (Box 327, Folder 2062)
  - Neurath and Kent, PNAS (Box 327, Folder 2062A)
  - New SPPS Reprints (Box 327, Folder 2063)
  - New SPPS Reprints (Box 327, Folder 2063A)
  - "A New Sulfur Heterocycle for Amino Group Protection in Peptide Synthesis" by Barany, 1977 (Box 327, Folder 2064-2065, Box 328, Folder 2066)
  - Nicolaou, K.C. (Box 328, Folder 2067)
  - Notecards (Box 328, Folder 2068-2070, Box 329, Folder 2071-2075, Box 330, Folder 2076-2081, Box 331, Folder 2082-2087, Box 332, Folder 2088)
  - Notecards and Notes (Box 332, Folder 2089)
  - "A Novel Synthetic Study of the Role of Arginine in the Bee Venom Neurotoxin, Apamin" by Cosand, 1976 (Box 332, Folder 2090)
  - Q (Box 332, Folder 2091)
  - "O-Glycopeptide Analogues of Enkephalin: FMOC-Amino Acid Glycoside Synthesis, Solid-Phase Glycopeptide Synthesis and Optimizations, and Pharmacology" by Mitchell, 1999 (Box 333, Folder 2092)
  - Old or Extra Figures ("Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis") (Box 333, Folder 2093)
  - Old Text ("Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis") (Box 334, Folder 2094)
  - Old Text ("Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis"), 1994 January 10 (Box 334, Folder 2095)
  - Old Text and Notes ("Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis") (Box 334, Folder 2096)
  - Old Versions (Box 334, Folder 2097)
  - Our Cecropin Papers (Merrifield), 1982-1996 (Box 335, Folder 2098)
  - Ovid Citations (Box 335, Folder 2099)
  - Oxytocin (Box 335, Folder 2100)
  - P (Box 335, Folder 2101)
  - Pan-American Association of Biochemical Societies, Revista (Box 335, Folder 2102)
  - Papers for Review (Box 335, Folder 2103)
  - Papers Referenced in Asn-Gly Paper (Box 336, Folder 2104)
  - Park (Box 336, Folder 2105)
  - Park (Box 336, Folder 2105A)
  - Patarroyo, Manuel Elkin (Box 336, Folder 2106-2108)
  - Peptide Resins (Box 336, Folder 2109)
  - Peptide Synthesis (Box 337, Folder 2110)
  - The Peptides (Box 337, Folder 2111)
  - Peptides (Box 337, Folder 2112)
  - "Peptides 1988," Proceedings of the 20th European Peptide Symposium (Box 337, Folder 2113)
  - Peptides Prepared by Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis (Box 337, Folder 2114)
  - Peptides: Synthesis and Applications, edited by B. Gutte (Box 337, Folder 2115)
  - Peptides: Synthesis and Applications, Chapter 2/3, "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Merrifield (Box 337, Folder 2116, Box 338, Folder 2117-2118)
  - Pert (Box 338, Folder 2119)
  - Photographs Added 1/4/1990, with Legends (Box 338, Folder 2120)
  - Photography, Drawings, Tables (Box 338, Folder 2121)
  - PNAS Manuscripts (Box 338, Folder 2122)
  - PNAS Manuscripts (Box 338, Folder 2122A)
  - Potts, John T. (Box 339, Folder 2123)
  - "Preparation of a Tertiaryalkyloxycarbonylhydrazide Resin and Its Application to Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Wang and Merrifield (Box 339, Folder 2124)
  - "Preparation of Some New Biphenylisopropyloxycarbonyl Amino Acids and their Application to the Solid Phase Synthesis of a Tryptophan-Containing Heptapeptide" by Wang and Merrifield (Box 339, Folder 2125)
  - "Probing the Functional Conformation of the Neuropeptide CGRP (Calcitonin Gene-Related Peptide)" by Lynch, 1989 (Box 339, Folder 2126)
  - "Profiles and Pathways in Organic Chemistry" Outline and Notes (Box 339, Folder 2127)
  - "Purificao, Sequenciamento, Sntese e Caracterizao Farmacolgica Parcial de um Pentadecapeptdeo Presente na Albumina do Rato" by Izumi, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 2128)
  - References (Box 339, Folder 2129)
  - References and Notes ("Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis") (Box 339, Folder 2130)
  - References, Chapter 2, "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by R.B. Merrifield, in Peptides: Synthesis and Application, edited by B. Gutte (Box 340, Folder 2131)
  - References for The History of Protein Syntheses, VG Phosphopeptides (Box 340, Folder 2132)
  - References for The History of Protein Syntheses, Figures (Box 340, Folder 2133)
  - References for The History of Protein Syntheses, Papers Already Used (Box 340, Folder 2134)
  - References for The History of Protein Syntheses, Sakakibara (Box 340, Folder 2135)
  - References for The History of Protein Syntheses, Unlabeled Folder (Box 340, Folder 2136-2137, Box 341, Folder 2138-2141, Box 342, Folder 2142)
  - References/Reviews To Be Used: Chronological (Box 342, Folder 2143)
  - "The Relation of Predicted Structure to Observed Conformation and Activity of Glucagon Analogs Containing Replacements at Positions 19, 22, and 23" by Merrifield et al. (Box 342, Folder 2144)
  - "Relationships between Structure and Biological Function in Analogs of RNase A-Peptide" by Levitt, 1972 (Box 342, Folder 2145)
  - Reprints (Box 342, Folder 2146-2147, Box 343, Folder 2148)
  - Reprints by Others, A (Box 343, Folder 2149)
  - Reprints by Others, B (Box 343, Folder 2150)
  - Reprints by Others, C (Box 343, Folder 2151)
  - Reprints by Others, D (Box 343, Folder 2152)
  - Reprints by Others, Dunn, Max S. (Box 344, Folder 2153)
  - Reprints by Others, F (Box 344, Folder 2154)
  - Reprints by Others, G (Box 344, Folder 2155)
  - Reprints by Others, H (Box 344, Folder 2156)
  - Reprints by Others, I (Box 344, Folder 2157)
  - Reprints by Others, J (Box 345, Folder 2158)
  - Reprints by Others, K (Box 345, Folder 2159)
  - Reprints by Others, L (Box 345, Folder 2160)
  - Reprints by Others, M (Box 345, Folder 2161)
  - Reprints by Others, N (Box 345, Folder 2162)
  - Reprints by Others, O (Box 345, Folder 2163)
  - Reprints by Others, P (Box 345, Folder 2164)
  - Reprints by Others, R (Box 346, Folder 2165)
  - Reprints by Unson, Woolley (Box 346, Folder 2166)
  - Reprints and Manuals (Box 346, Folder 2167)
  - "Retro and Retroenantio Analogs of Cecropin-Melittin Hybrids" by Merrifield et al. (Box 346, Folder 2168)
  - Retro Papers (Box 346, Folder 2169)
  - RNase Slide Material (Box 347, Folder 2170)
  - Rodman, PNAS (Box 347, Folder 2171)
  - Rodman, PNAS (Box 347, Folder 2171A)
  - Rough Draft of "The Proteins" (Box 347, Folder 2172)
  - S (Box 347, Folder 2173, Box 348, Folder 2174-2176)
  - Sakakibara (Box 348, Folder 2177)
  - Sakakibara (Box 348, Folder 2177A)
  - Sakmar (Box 349, Folder 2178)
  - Sakmar, Thomas P. et al., "Tyrosine Sulfation of CCR5 N-Terminal Peptide by Tyrosylprotein Sulfotransferases 1 and 2 Follows a Discrete Pattern and Temporal Sequence" (Box 349, Folder 2179)
  - Salmon, PNAS (Box 349, Folder 2180)
  - Salmon, PNAS (Box 349, Folder 2180A)
  - Samanen (Box 349, Folder 2181)
  - Sapse, Anne-Marie (Box 349, Folder 2182)
  - Sardana, Mohinder K. (Box 349, Folder 2183)
  - Sarin, Synthetic Efficiency (Box 349, Folder 2184)
  - Sarin, Synthetic Efficiency (Box 349, Folder 2184A)
  - Sarin, Synthetic Efficiency (Box 349, Folder 2185)
  - Schally (Box 349, Folder 2186)
  - Schlesinger, David H. (Box 350, Folder 2187)
  - "Science" Manuscripts and Drafts, Koshland (Box 350, Folder 2188)
  - Seebach (Box 350, Folder 2189)
  - Sehgal (Box 350, Folder 2190)
  - Sehgal, 2 Interferon Publications (Box 350, Folder 2191)
  - Seitz, Riehl (Draft, Stalin's Captive: Nikolaus Riehl and the Soviety Race for the Bomb) (Box 350, Folder 2192)
  - Selected Recent Reprints of Professor George Barany (Box 351, Folder 2193)
  - "Selective Deprotection of the N-tert-Butyloxycarbonyl Group in Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis with Chlorotrimethylsilane in Phenol" by Kaiser et al., OId Version (Box 351, Folder 2194)
  - "Semisynthetic Peptides and Proteins," Chaiken (Box 351, Folder 2195)
  - SEP, 2002-2003 (Box 351, Folder 2196)
  - Silhouette (Box 351, Folder 2197)
  - Sklyarof (Box 351, Folder 2198)
  - Slide Drawings, 1985 (Box 351, Folder 2199)
  - Slide Material for Summer 1984 (Box 351, Folder 2200)
  - Slides (Box 351, Folder 2201)
  - Slides to be Made (Box 351, Folder 2202)
  - Smith, Tam, PNAS (Box 352, Folder 2203)
  - Smith, Tam, PNAS (Box 352, Folder 2203A)
  - "A Solid Phase-Fragment Approach to Peptide Synthesis" by Wang and Merrifield (Box 352, Folder 2204)
  - Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis (Box 352, Folder 2205-2206)
  - "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis after 25 Years: The Design and Synthesis of Antagonists of Glucagon" by Merrifield (Box 352, Folder 2207)
  - Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis Bibliography, 1-100 (Box 353, Folder 2208)
  - Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis Bibliography, 101-239 (Box 353, Folder 2209)
  - Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis Biology (Box 353, Folder 2210)
  - Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis Chemistry (Box 353, Folder 2211)
  - "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis," Erickson (Box 353, Folder 2212)
  - "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Erickson and Merrifield (Box 354, Folder 2213)
  - "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Erickson and Merrifield, 1974 (Box 354, Folder 2214)
  - "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Merrifield (Box 355, Folder 2215)
  - "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis: New Chemistry and New Directions" by Bruce Merrifield (Box 355, Folder 2216)
  - "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" Review (Box 355, Folder 2217)
  - "Solid Phase Precipitation and Extraction (SPPE), a New Separation Process applied to the Isolation of Synthetic Peptides" by Bonner et al. (Box 355, Folder 2218)
  - "Solid Phase Synthesis of the Cyclo-Dodecadepsipeptide Valinomycin" by Gisin, Merrifield, and Tosteson (Box 355, Folder 2219)
  - "Solid Phase Synthesis: The Use of Solid Supports and Insoluble Reagents in Peptide Synthesis (Chapter 3)" (Box 355, Folder 2220)
  - "The Solution Conformation of Oxytocin" by Fischman, 1978 (Box 356, Folder 2221)
  - "The Solution Photochemistry of Simple Cyclopentenones" by Smith, 1972 (Box 356, Folder 2222)
  - "Some New Aspects of the Relationship of Chemical Structure to Biological Activity" by D.W. Woolley, 1944 (Box 356, Folder 2223)
  - "The Specific Carboxymethylation of the Amino Groups of Human Hemoglobin: Structural and Functional Implications" by Fantl, 1985 (Box 356, Folder 2224)
  - "Specificity and Neutralizing Capacity of Antibodies Elicited by a Synthetic Peptide of Scorpion Toxin" by Van Rietschoten et al., PNAS (Box 356, Folder 2225)
  - "Specificity and Neutralizing Capacity of Antibodies Elicited by a Synthetic Peptide of Scorpion Toxin" by Van Rietschoten et al., PNAS (Box 356, Folder 2225A)
  - SPPS Bibliography and Numbers to Adv. Enz. Refs. (Box 356, Folder 2226)
  - SPPS Prints (Box 356, Folder 2227, Box 357, Folder 2228-2231, Box 358, Folder 2232)